Contact

tammykent51289@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tamarakent-2112ab9a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Meditech
Epic Systems
Cerner

Tamara Kent

Travel Nurse at Parallon Workforce Solutions Mars Hill, North Carolina

Summary

Registered Nurse with 15
years experience. Strong capacity to multitask; manage care of patients
with competing priorities with ease while providing safe, competent, and publication priorities with ease while providing safe, competent, and publicate ability to assess and advocate for patient needs, develop and plans and maintain patient medical records. Clinical knowledge and profit Strong interpersonal and communication skills; experienced in collaboration interdisciplinary team for optimal delivery of patient care.

Knowledge of official medical coding guidelines, CMS, and private payer regulations related to the Inpatient Profit an ability to analyze and interpret medical record documentation and form

queries; and an ability to benchmark and analyze clinical documentation;

Experience

Parallon Workforce Solutions
Travel Nurse

Trinity Healthcare Staffing Group
Travel Registered Nurse
January 2017 - Present (3 years 7 months)
Spartanburg, South Carolina

Pulmonary Telemetry Unit

Mission Health
Registered Nurse
July 2003 - Present (17 years 1 month)

MedStaff Travel Registered Nurse August 2013 - February 2014 (7 months)

Arcadia Home Care & Staffing Registered Nurse February 2010 - January 2011 (1 year)

Education

Lees-McRae College
Bachelor of Applied Science (B.A.Sc.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2011 - 2013)

Mayland Community College
Associate of Science (A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2001 - 2003)